Hello everyone, this is Hitomi Takamatsu from Equal Love.
Yes, that's right, it's the Equal Love Moat Race!
What a surprise! Mr. Hamanaka from Moat Race came to see us!
Thank you very much.
Thank you for the third time!
Thank you so much!
Yes, so far I've been here with Mininya, but this time
But this time, we've got this girl here for the first time.
Please come in.
Hello, nice to meet you.
I'm Morasana.
Yay! Thank you.
Have you ever done a motorsport race before?
I've never done one, but I'm just saying that I think we'll see some beginner's luck from Sana today.
I know you're going to take over the mininha today.
I'd like to take over the mininha box.
I think we'll both win today.
And what a surprise, Mr. Takasugi is here again this time!
Nice to meet you.
Thank you for visiting us again
Goddess of Victory
Let's do our best.
I hope you can teach me a lot today as well.
I look forward to working with you.
Today, Races 2 and 3 will be shown on the Ikono Igoi channel.
Races 5 and 6 will be distributed by Boat Race Hamanaka Channel! Races 5 and 6 will be distributed by Boat Race Hamanaka Channel!
And this time, we will not only predict the races, but we will also have a special project!
Please look forward to it until the end!
So, two races are already on display!
I'd like to make a prediction right away!
I wonder if the exhibition was switched.
It looked like it was in there.
But I don't like it.
But wait, the most popular 234 in the second race.
That's right.
There's not a single 1.
The first boat is a recent complaint, or rather...
There's a Class-A player outside of it, so there's that one.
But I'm really interested in the No. 5 boat.
Five in three is pretty good, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Class-A boats are in 2, 3 and 4.
If he gets a good shot at the inside, there's no membrane to get out.
Maybe he's trying to make a move.
I'd like to attack from the inside, even if only a little.
Maybe he was trying to take advantage of the development.
We're really talking about something else.
I have no idea.
Well, for the first time, he's giving you a little bit of chicken in a race that comes before the race.
I'll give it to you on the card.
This race is hard.This race is so hard!
It's difficult!
It's a little irregular and difficult.
How do you choose this course?
There are so many detailed rules.
If you're going for the inside of the field with the front
the start line is closer to the start line.
The sinking is deeper.
And that makes it a little more difficult
I don't know if I can hold it or not.
I'm not sure if I can hold it or not.
I'm taking the risk of going inside the frame.
Red!
Red is No. 1!
What? I'm in 3.
What? Isn't it good?
3 is so good.
Three's good.
How much did you spend? Here.
I went for 1.
A hundred.
I spent more.
I don't have an eraser.
I have to spend 10,000 yen this time for races 2 and 3.
Oh, what?
So you're okay with 30 or something?So you're okay with 30 or something?
Yes, that's fine.
Tell me!
Can I spend $5,000 on this race?
Can I become one?
Will you be a Kan-nin?
You're going to be a Kan'nin?
Isn't this a test?
This looks like a test.
Let's do a test with a marker.
I'm 4 points ahead.
Oh, no, no, no.
Wait a minute.
But if it's like the exhibit...
The third boat with the fastest time will be in the corner.
There is a possibility that he might go in from the corner.
But there might be a psychological reason for that frame.
But either way, I'm a little bit worried about the inside.
I'm thinking two or three boats would be my target.
Thank you very much.
I'll put this out there just in case.
Yes, I'd like to canig.
I want to canig.
234, 2345.
I mean, 234 is pretty popular.
I'm sure the fifth boat is coming into full bloom, but... The fifth boat is coming to full bloom, though.
I've made it to three.
Oh no, I see.
Time's running out, time's running out.
You're doing it like you're used to it.
You're like an ATM in Ginza.
Oh, no, tell me, tell me, tell me.
Then put the money in first.
Where do I put the money?
This way?
Oh, no.
Here, put this in.
Two in a row?
Two in a row? Overlap them?
Okay, okay.
Boxes? Boxes?
Boxes?
I got it, I got it!
You got it?
I got it! Look!
I got Sona, too!
I did it! For the first time in my life.
What county?
What was it again?
I thought it was ping-pong. I thought it was a ping-pong county.
Boat county!
Boat county.
I'm so happy!
I bought it!
My first one! I want to win!
If I buy this...
Is it your money?
No?
No!
Parts?
Yes, first of all, the boxes, the Mirinyan boxes.
I bought one, three, five.
And then the triplet ones.
The first one is 2, 3, 4 and the second one is
Three, two, four.
The popular one.
And the slightly popular one.
Eh, the one you're buying 1,000 yen for?
Eh, 1,000 yen. 1,000 yen.
F5.
Seriously, F5?
It's my first time.
I don't know anything anymore.
I know it's popular, but if it goes the way it's going now... It's popular, but if it goes the way it's going now
It's going to be priced right.
I've narrowed it down quite a bit.
Even if the payout is low, it's a big plus.
Oh, really?
Okay, I'll take
One.
Do you have a 2,3,5 box?
I'm on the 5, but I'm really curious.
I haven't bought a box in a while.
Please win! Please!
Here we go!
How do you know which one is the best?
White is number one.
Black is number two.
Red is number three.
It's a frame.
So, Sanna's green, so there's 6.
Hand #6.
So, if you're interested in 6 next time, put 6 in.
Oh, next.
You're in.
Oh, you're back?
I've been betrayed!
I've been betrayed! I've been betrayed!
Wasn't there? Start Exhibition
We got in right out of the box!
We were betrayed.
When you end up going in at the start of the frame...
Do you feel like you've been betrayed?
No, the inside resists.
Then, you give up and go to the end of the line.
And now race two is about to begin.
Come on!
Two against four!
Three and a five?
Two against four. Isn't that unusual?
Yes, they're starting.
What, two against four?
Who am I supposed to root for?
Which one?
The President of the CPC 溤 together
Wow, just 1 thấy.
1 won!
Wright.
1, 1, 1, 1!
No one saw that coming.
Wow.
Nobody saw that coming.
What? Oh, what?
Oh, it's not one? This isn't one?
But one, three, five is this one.
Oh, that's what you mean?
Oh, I got 2!
No, you didn't.
Kaneko!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Wow!
Wow, that's quite something today.
Oh, but, oh, oh,
Is it because of the wind?
But you mean 2, 3, and 4 should be in already?
Yeah.
Who's 4?
Hey, Blue, give me a little more!
Please!
Come on!
But I still get it, I still get it, I still get it.
I can still do it,
Blue, Blue, I want you to try harder.
Wow!
Wow, Mr. Ichiiichi!
But 2 is here, isn't it?
2 is here!
It was 1, wasn't it? It was pretty much 1, because at first
It was pretty much 1.
You know...
Mm-hmm.
You're coming.
Wow, that's a deal.
Two, one, three.
Forty-three times 40.3.
Oh, that's frustrating!
Wow!
Yukichin.
End. End.
Wow, that's cool.
So cool!
Oh, man, it's over. Half done.
It's half over.
There's only four minutes left.
Only one more race left.
Samples?
Rehearsal.
It's worth 4,030 yen.
Are you going to do this rehearsal like the real thing?
It's just the first part of the rehearsal.
What?
We're in a different order. Because the order changed.
Because I had muscles.
I had muscles.
I thought rehearsal is supposed to be the same as the actual performance.
But that was really, really unusual.
Unusual.
The current was different, too. Two against four.
The third boat was a dash.
That's what I want to do.
The slow start and the dash start are totally different.
Then, the fifth boat made me crazy.
He drove me crazy.
It's frustrating, but fun.
It's fun today, too.
The wind is blowing from the stands today.
It's a little bit of a wall because of this building.
So there's not a lot of wind on the water.
Oh my God, we have to win this!
If we don't win this, it's going to be the end of the first half of the channel.
Then we'll end up with zero.
It's true.
Matsuda is strong, too, Dad.
He is.
Three races!
The favorite is up to 18 points.
Is it broken?Is it cracked?
Oh, man, this is gonna cost a fortune.
It'd be great if we hit it.
Does it look great?
Hey, I wish I could cheer you on from the front.
I'd love to cheer you on from the front.
I'm a little worried about the inside.
They're both running.
And in race three, he's running away.
I'm a little bit...
You're a little bit deceived, aren't you?
I'm deceived.
He's commenting.
Is he commenting?
The first boat wasn't as bad as I thought, but if it's a body at the slit, it might be stretched.
Boat 2 managed to get away, but she's still weak overall.
Boat three, I think the tilt is a negative, so I'll think about adjusting it.
Boat No. 4 was not suitable for the boat because we could not get a grip on the adjustment.
Boat No. 5, the waist is better than the forward tilt.
Boat No. 6, the direction of the boat for a moment is good, but I want to have a leg from there.
It's not very good, is it?
Yes, everyone's comments are a little bit negative.
There are local players in boats No. 2 and No. 4.
Some people say they haven't been able to adjust.
But it's amazing how many runaways there were today.
It's worrisome. I'm curious.
I'm going to confuse you, aren't I?
If it were true, I'd like to go to Niigata or something.
I'm wondering if I have to hold back on the shades, too.
I have to buy 600 yen worth.
I'm predicting six points now.
Two, three, four, two, three, four, six for the third.
I liked Matsuda, but inside
Two of the Class A 2,3,4 remained in first and second place
Matsuda was in 3rd place after pushing 6.
I believe that.
That's a lot of pressure.
You're abandoning the first.
I'm still curious about the 1.
But the odds are against him.
I don't mind going a little wide.
But the comment about the first hand isn't as bad as I thought it would be.
He said the slit torso can be stretched.
What's a slit?
A slit is a picture of a slit when you start.
The slit photo is taken at the start of the race.
The lines are equally spaced from 0 to 1 second.
The slit photo is taken from 0 to 1 second at equal intervals.
There is a theory of boat racing.
I was asked today to explain it with a magnet.
I was asked to explain it with a magnet today. I'm being told today, so...
I'm grateful.
The real thing.
I think there's a lot of different ways to do it.
I think there are a lot of ways to do it.
I'm going to try to explain it in a nutshell.
Boat racing...
First of all, if the first boat goes around first
If the first one goes first, he becomes a runner...
But if the first one goes first and comes in first, he becomes a runner.
If you cross the line and insert your hand, it's called "shinshin".
So, the foot, the ichigo hand, for example, goes around first.
If you hit the head of the No. 2 move, and the No. 3 move comes in between the two, then the No. 1 move is indicated, but the No. 2 move is indicated.
This means that the 1st move is being played, but the 2nd move is being played.
It's a "roll-up".
And it doesn't matter if it's 2 or 3.
If it comes out as it is, it is Makuri.
And there's also "blessed.
What is "blessed"?
Blessed" means that the person is flying and disappears, and you can get the first place.
You can be blessed and get the first place.
And then there's also pulling out.
Like in the race we were in, when the second one pointed to us and we were in first place.
So there are times when you have to pull out of a race.
Basically, the first player runs away first, and then the second player
And then the second player points to it.Then move 2 points to it.
Move 3 outside of it goes to the outside.
Move No. 4 can point above or below where this 2 is pointing.
That's all there is.
Move No. 5 is going to roll up where move No. 3 is holding, and aim at the point where move No. 5 inserts.
Hand No. 5 will aim at the point where hand No. 3 rolls its grip and inserts it.
Hand No. 6 usually inserts the root at the end.
It's like a boat race theory.
We'll start from there, and we'll say, "Well, this guy's fast, so he's going to go around.
Or, "This guy is fast, so he's going to go around," or, "This guy is going to go around from the second course," and so on.
Let's make a prediction!
Thank you very much.
First of all, I continued to buy the mini-box that I mentioned earlier.
And this is called Iori Box.
I bought this one because it was Iori's birthday.
IOLI
Looks like a winner!
Good luck Iori!
Next, this was recommended by Mr. Takahashi.
I thought I would probably win if I bought this one, so I bought it!
My member color is green.
I bought only 6 tickets just because he wanted me to buy the green one.
And I bought all the rest.
All six.
I've never heard of buying all 6.
Whip is a scary thing, isn't it? I mean whips are scary.
If I win, if I can buy everything in the green car.
That's right.
I'm making today a box day.
I'm trying to tie it in with 126, and...
I'm kind of thinking about Pavilion No. 5 today.
It's the day I'm thinking about Pavilion No. 5, and I have two goals.
I hope I'll win!
I hope I win!
I'll eat this.
I eat this when I don't win. It's been a while since I've had a reset meal.
If you're losing now, eat this. I'm losing, right?
I'll have some now that no one else is eating.
I'll have one too. Let's reset.
It's a specialty of Scolab boat races.
It's reset. I'll win.
I'm going to win. Let's go.
Matsuda-san's in. Matsuda-san's in A1. My dad says he's the best.
Maybe that's what a second father says.
Thanks to Sara, we're going back to the green car.
Green car
That's right.
Three races are starting. Good luck.
Oh, Mr. Matsuda! Matsuda-san! Matsuda-san, green! Good luck, Mr. Green!
They're all here! It's all here!
Wow! One! One! Matsuda-san! Matsuda-san! Go for it! You can do it! I can do it! Wow! One! One! Matsuda-san! Matsuda-san! Go for it! You can do it! I can do it!
Hold on! I'm doing it right now! From here! From here! From the top! From here!
Here!
Carry the green on your back!
Green power!
Green power! Green power!
Cheer up, Green!
I'm cheering for you!
More green!
Matsuda san can do it!
You can do it, Matsuda san!
You can do it!
Matsuda san!
I'm still within range!
Please! Please! Please! Please!
I can make it, Matsuda-san!
Mr. Matsuda came to me in a dream today.
I'm so disappointed.
A little tougher.
One, two, three times.
I'll run away.
No, I'm going to run away.
Wow, that's frustrating.
I won one, two, six times.
Mr. Matsuda!
One, two, three.
It was 1,2,3...
Thank you so much for your hard work.
The highlight of the show.
I'm so sorry.
It's so frustrating.
I've been off by one since a while ago.
It's over.
No way!
It'll probably be over in about five minutes.
No, it'll be over in a single cut.
What a short video!
But they're coming.
He's going to run away, isn't he? I'm gonna run away.
Do you want to do the math?
You don't have to.
Let's do the math.
So, in the blink of an eye.
Races two and three were over in the blink of an eye.
As you can see
Start rate
0%.
Ha-ha-ha-ha
I mean 0%.
But it was difficult.
Yes, it was.
It was difficult, wasn't it?
Very difficult.
It was my first time in school.
It was my first time.
I was in a bad way with the actress channel, so I went to the second half of the show.
I was not doing well in the second half
Boat Race on the Manako Channel.
I'm sure we
I'm sure we've already beaten them to the punch.
We'll definitely come in the green car.
We're going to win the green car in the green car.
That's right.
I'm counting on you. Best regards
The second part of this
Boat Race will be on the Manako Channel.
I hope you will all support our brave men and women!
But before that, in this video, we're going to have a talk with the players after this.
Thank you very much.
I'll finally have a chance to talk with a current boat racer.
I'm looking forward to it!
Okay, everyone, please join us.
So, we've moved on from the boat race track.
I'm here at the main office in charge of Hamamatsu!
Yay!
I heard it's a restaurant that serves training food.
Have you ever had a training course?
I haven't!
Neither have I, and this is the first time I've been to such a restaurant in Shizuoka!
I'm glad to hear that.
An active boat racer!
And a female racer!
I heard that two of them are here.
We don't know who they are yet.
We're kind of nervous.
It's the first time we've met the current boat racers.
That's right.
You said just now.
Yeah, I don't have any friends.That's right, I don't have any friends.
That's right, I don't normally have any.
It's not a surprise or anything.
We're both a little fucked up.
It's not some kind of surprise show.
Stop it. From behind.
Stop being so paranoid. You're freaking me out.
My back. Oh, my God.
Come on, come on, come on.
Please, please, please, please.
I'm not gonna look yet.
Okay, here we go.
Okay, close your eyes.
I'm not closing my eyes.
I'll call for you.
They don't even read my eyes anymore.
Momoi Shibata and Maoya Kawai.
Oh, no.
Shut up!
I'm sorry.
I'm scared.
It's so obvious.
It's so shiny.
It's like you really don't have a choice.
Let me introduce myself again.
Shibata, please. Maaya Shibata, please.
I am Maaya Shibata from the Shizuoka Branch.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Maya Kawai from the Shizuoka Branch.
It's Moe!
I screamed so hard!
I saw the moment I screamed!
It was an intense moment.
That's great.
How old are you?
I'm 24.
I'm 21.
Oh, Moe.
What?
I'm just trying to swallow.
You're young.
What should I call you?
Certainly.
What?
Momochan.
Moe-chan.
Yes, Moe-chan.
Momochan and Moe-chan?
Moe-chan.
Do you have any basics? What are the basics?
Basics like Hitomi.
Hitomi.
I'm Sanatsu.
Sunatsu.
Oh.
Then Hitomi and Sanatsu.
Okay.
Uh...
Girls...
A girl!
So cute.
Let's have a drink.
You drink this kind of stuff?
Tea or water?
What?
I don't drink at all.
Do you drink soda?
Yes, I do.
Do you drink normally?
I see.
I might ask you some questions today.
Please do. Please.
First boat drink?
Yes, sir.
The word I learned today is "sass.
I'll be happy when I learn to roll.
I've heard a little bit of it, too.
Okay, I'll have a ginger ale.
I'll have a cola.
Uron tea.
I knew it!
I knew it.
I'd heard since the summer we might meet.
I've been looking forward to it.
Your father's going to meet Moe, too, right?
Yeah.
I'll go see him.
I was really looking forward to it.
But the other one was a secret.
Just now...
Moe-chan, who was screaming...
Moe-chan!
I don't mean to be rude, but...
But you don't look like a boat racer at all.
You don't look like you're doing boat racing.
I'm told I don't.
Like that. Something like that.
Do you usually do it with the fish maw on?
I do.
Oh, wow.
You do it with the fish maw on?
Masachan, is that right?
I can take pictures.
Can you film it?
Yes, but...
Eventually, yes.
Fishmoths are always filming me.
I see.
There are a lot of people here.
What?
Lots of people.
Welcome.
How tall are you?
I thought you were very petite.
I'm 154.
What? Petite.
Petite?
I'm 153.
Ehh...
I'd be just right for him here.
Oh, I see.
The smallest girl in the rec room. The tiniest little girl in the rec room.
About 149.
Wow.
That's big.
Fifty-eight.
Wow.
If you had 63, you wouldn't be able to do it, would you?
Yes, you can.
Can you?
The biggest girl I know is 167.
That much?
You need to lose weight.
Of course.
Antle's toast.
What do you mean?
Yes, there's a word for that.
In Hamamatsu, Enshu, a town known for success.
In Hamamatsu, Enshu, a town known for its success, there's a word, Yaramaika.
Yaramaika" means "Let's do it!
Let's do it, let's do it, let's do it.
Let's do it!
If I say I'm in the prime of my career...
One of you says, "Let's do it.
The rest of us say, "Hey!" and toast.
Our Mr. Morohashi will do it.
It's the Yaramaika's job. It's a job for Yaramaika.
That's what you were called in for.
Barmore style.
It's the height of your career, please.
Yaramaika
Come on.
Are you okay? This is it.
Enjoy your stay.
We'll see you in a few minutes.
Thank you very much.
Thank you so much.
I didn't realize your voice was so loud.
Are you in a weight-loss period or something?
No, I'm not.
No, I'm fine.
In fact, I need to gain some.
I didn't know that was a thing.
I'm supposed to weigh at least 47 kilograms.
If I'm lighter than that, I have to put on weight.
I'm a little heavy.
It's more weight than weight.
Then let's eat a lot.
Are you careful about your weight?
When you have two shows...
Do you have a set list, like the order of the songs? A set list is a list of songs in a certain order.
It depends on the order of the songs.
Sometimes I lose 3 kilos in a day.
Singing and dancing are very calorie-dense.
It's very special, isn't it?
That might be true.
Sometimes it's easy to lose weight, sometimes it's hard to gain weight.
Sometimes it's easy to gain weight.
Sometimes it's easy to gain weight and sometimes it's hard to lose weight.
I go to the sauna a lot.
I love sauna.
Are saunas popular?
Yes, it's very popular.
Is it popular?
When there's a sauna in the dormitory...
Oh, wow.
I love it!
I'm so jealous!
Is that where you'll be staying?
Yes, during the race.
I'll be with you the whole time.
During the week.
We all eat at the same place.
Is there a sauna?
Yes, we go there.
Oh, that's nice. Eh, I like it.
Ew.
There are times when I care and times when I don't.
Maybe it's similar.
It's like our concerts are like conventions.
Music videos, music video shoots...
I want you to sing that one.
Summer... what is it?
Summary
Summer summary
Where would you like to see it?
I'm in the groove!
Where would you like to go?
I'm in a groove.
I'm in the groove.
It's like Let's Go.
One, two, three, four.
The first part.
Let's go.
All right.
Cute.
I'm so happy
You sing as many steps as you can, don't you?
Do you have a lot of things you want to do?
Do you have time off?
No, I don't have time off, except for practice and training. On my days off, I don't practice or train or anything like that.
I have my own time.
But when I can, I go to practice.
There he is today, Hamanaka.
Yes, he was.
Oh, really?
I don't know.
I didn't notice.
I have private time.
Do you go shopping?
I do.
I buy bags.
Why did you decide to take port lessons?
My father suggested I try it.
He told me too.
He told you?
And how did you do that?
I went to see Hamanaka.
I saw a girl running and riding.
I thought it was cool.
So I did.
Eventually, I wanted to do it myself.
I wanted to do it by myself.
I had never exercised before.
I worked hard for one exam. I worked hard for one exam.
And when was that?
13?
15? !
I was in the 13th grade.
That's great.
Seniors and juniors?
No?
About three years.
Three years?
Yes.
I started when you were very young.
That's true.
It's been a long time.
The trees are far apart, aren't they?
We're only two years apart.
Are you like friends?
I don't feel like we're that far apart.
We don't feel that far apart.
Close.
She's like a junior.
He's so cute.
She seems like she's 21.
She's cute.
How did you get started, Momoi?
What made me start? How did you get started?
Did you meet someone?
My parents recommended it to me.
That's great.
I went to see him at Hamanaka, too.
And then I saw Momoi-san's debut.
What?
It wasn't my debut.
It was Hamanaka's debut.
I was just taking his picture.
What? That's great!
In the race chart, there's a name like Momoi Shibata
Momoi Shibata, who debuted this week.
Was that 17?
17 or 18?
I thought it was amazing for a high school student.
I thought, "I'd like to take his place right away.
That's amazing.
Well, there are a lot of things. Today is the first time for me to do so many things.
What is your favorite food?
My favorite food is muscat.
So, you want to join the Ichora Club?
Yes, I do.
Is there one every time? Yes, every time.
Everyone likes them.
Sometimes they give them to us at concerts. You sometimes give them to us at concerts.
Yes, they do.
My favorite food is ramen and potatoes.
How cute!
I often go to McDonald's.
I love McDonald's.
It's delicious.
It's the best.
They have fries.
Yes, they do! We have fries.
Are there times when you want to eat them, but you have to hold back?
Yes, I do. I gained a little weight during my flying vacations, so I've been holding back lately.
What do you do during your flying vacations?
Practice.
Basically, I practice.
Yes, I do. Basic practice.
So you go with them to practice?
Yes, we do.
Every day?
Every day. It's a six-day session, so it's like going for six days in a row and then having a short break.
What do you think about when you start?
I feel nervous. I feel like I'm flying.
Do you know?
I'm already divided.
Wow! You are scared.
You are scared. You are scared.
I'm always scared.
Like a month off if this thing sticks out even a little bit.
Aah!
But you should go on the offensive.
Because if you don't, you can't win.
You're starting, right? Is it cold?
Aah!
I was thinking that so much today, and the temperature is dropping rapidly.
It's cold in winter.
And the light.
The light is cold.
The light is cold?
Is it cold?
From now on!
It's cold! Cold! It's cold!
It's better to have a cold at the Maku Tower.
It's not colder in Makutate.
It's not cold.
And then they would have to pass the oroni.
I see.
What is the most expensive thing you bought recently?
This, this, this.
Here you go.
Really, sir, please let me out. Oh, really, doctor, please let me out.
Oh, are you sure?
It's a program, isn't it?
I've never seen you on the show before.
No, no, no.
It was just a show.
This is expensive.
Extra race? There's an extra race.
That just came in,
I spent all the money I had for that.
I decided I had had enough and bought it on my way home from Tokyo.
Wow, that's cool. I bought it.
It's cool.
What are you going to spend your money on? Finally.
Beauty?
No, really! Yes, it's good.
Esthetics.
And body esthetics.
It's tiring, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
It was really fun doing it for the first time today.
I really didn't know what was going on at first.
Once you win like this, it's like a swamp.
It's a swamp, isn't it? It's a swamp.
You can't stop.
You want to make more, don't you?
That's right.
Is there any pressure?
Every time.
When I get a big prize.
I'm not very good at winning the first place.
Sold, sold, sold.
Do you look at it before the race?
I try not to look at it before a race.
I look at it and think, "Oh my God.
Do you get nervous about the first place?
I do get nervous.
The time of the ligature is the best.
I'm most comfortable with 6.
What?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You got 100 5 yen yaki.
Eh~.
I'm sorry.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
I want to take a picture. I want to take a picture.
Let's take a picture.
I want to take a picture.
Here is a crispy introduction to vegetables.
We wonder how much is there.
The customer connects 5 yen.
Thank you very much.
Amazing.
Wait a minute.
May I?
I think I'll go ahead and do it first.
Let's go.
How many are there?
A hundred.
A hundred?
May I?
Ready.
Bon appétit.
Yum.
Yum!
What do the idols eat?
Cup noodles and...
They eat ramen?
I also like to make carpaccio. And I like making carpaccio a lot.
We're having carpaccio.
What was that? We're having carpaccio.
Carpaccio is...
Raw fish in olive oil.
Make the sauce.
It's really easy to make sauce.
I eat it with this.
I eat everything!
I also ate ramen yesterday.
Ramen, chicken and tapioca!
So cute!
I eat a lot of cup ramen, don't you?
I really do!
I dance so I can lose weight.
Before a concert...
Be careful.
I like your skin.
You have really nice skin.
Do you have any foundation recommendations?
That's how we got the word out.
What is it?
On Hitomi's Twitter.
"I use this cosmetics" on Twitter.
It got a lot of buzz. I did it and it got a lot of buzz.
Where is it from?
A Korean makeup foundation called Lilibeth.
It's a Korean makeup foundation.
It really doesn't break me out.
I think it even stays put after a shower.
Thank God for that.
I always sweat like a waterfall
I sweat like a waterfall when I go to live shows, but it doesn't break down.
It doesn't break up.
I've never talked to a celebrity before.
Come and play with us.
I'm playing with you.
Let's go hang out.
Are there 10 members?
Yes, I do.
Are you close?
We get along really well.
No, we're not.
If there were 10 members, we would definitely get along a little bit.
You don't get along with them?
They have a good way of getting along with each other.
Everyone respects the girls.
Every single one of them.
What I don't have, this girl definitely has.
I'm sure she has something I don't. I mean, there's something like that.
I can see that.
Not too girly?
It's more like a casual relationship.
How long have you been together?
Seven years.
We just had our 6th anniversary concert.
You've been together since you were a teenager, right?
I was 20, right?
I'm a big senior.
I've been playing since I was 12.
Mr. Cossie picked me.
How old were you when you started?
The games online group?
I was a child actor for a while.
I quit once.
How long have you been?
I've been doing this for over nine years.
That's amazing.
You've got the energy to start when you were very young.
It's like you wanted to stand out.
Like you wanted to make a name for yourself.
But I couldn't go to the field day because of work.
I couldn't go on field trips, so I stopped.
That's what kids do.
Cute. Cute.
My first game online at Equal Love.
I went online.
I was an imo... at first.
You were cute.
No, you weren't.
What are you talking about?
It was the cutest thing I've ever seen.
You were a potato.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, you were always the prettiest.
I was the center.
But then...
I couldn't talk to her anymore.
I haven't really changed.
You don't really interact with people who haven't really changed?
In the same chapter.
You know, girls from the same chapter.
Do you do that?
Like going out to dinner after a recipe?
I see.
Do you guys and girls get along with each other?
We are good friends.
We get along well.
Many people get married. Many people get married.
About half.
Half of the female athletes
Marry male athletes.
What? Wow.
That reminds me of something cool.
I don't know.
Boom.
Oh, cool.
30% more
Other than Hamanaka.
I'd like to hear about your favorite boat race track.
Let's hear it.
I like it here.
It's easy to do.
Hamanaka is the easiest place for me.
Of course.
You practice all the time.
It's my hometown.
Is it any different?
Not at all.
Have you ever been to Edogawa?
Yes, I have.
It's a river.
It's bad. That was bad.
It's bad there, isn't it?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's really hard to do.
I see.
Why is that?
Well, it's just the flow and everything.
These waves...
It's amazing.
It stings.
I'm in two pieces.
Two.
Busted.
No, not at all.
I was struggling to support myself... my body.
Did it not go as you expected?
Not at all.
It's very rough.
Rough.
I see.
Have two more.
Okay. - Okay.
Okay, I'm on it.
You want a ride? You want a ride?
Yes, that's right.
Two.
Shall we play?
Do you know a game called Doskoi?
I've never heard of it.
No, I don't.
I'm glad you don't know.
It's a relief.
I play it in collaboration.
Usually when I'm free backstage.
Takumanando koi!
4 letters
Boredom, come on!
Boredom!
I've already lost!
We've already lost!
That's right.